shopwss.com 2010-07-18

# Privacy Policy | ShopWSS.com

## **Privacy Policy**

ShopWss is committed to protecting your privacy. The following statement provides details about our privacy policy.

**Receiving Email Promotions**  
To receive promotions, offers, coupons and other specials you may subscribe(Opt-In) to the [**_WSS Email Exclusives_**](http://visitor.constantcontact.com/manage/optin?v=001CPbz0pBDAy7tDvRO_fnbZguuDPcZN7osg2IKJkZvzR7bxBfvxw4mPQ%3D%3D) mailing list for FREE! You may also select to receive or not to receive offers or other information from ShopWss.com upon your registration. At any time you may request to unsubscribe(Opt-Out) from our mailing list. To unsubscribe follow the link "Instant removal with SafeUnsubscribe™" at the bottom of the email you have received.

**Special Rules for Children**  
As a result of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, you must be at least 13 year old to register or make a purchase on our website.

**About Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are generally used to make our services more convenient and personalized.

Shopwss.com collects personal information voluntarily and only during website registration. The information collected includes contact information such e-mail address; and demographic information such as city and address. ShopWss.com may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our web site is used. Please note that ShopWss.com will not have access to your personal information unless you voluntarily provide it to us.

By using our web site, you consent to the privacy policy set forth above. ShopWss.com may change its privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toďż˝keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), our policy is located at.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.shopwss.com 

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 09.24.2009

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.shopwss.com  
13425 S Figueroa St  
Los Angeles, CA 90061  
USA  
cservice@warehouseshoesale.com  
1.800.276.2002
